Your final project in this course is going to be to write a sorting algorithm.
在本课程中，你的最后一个项目将是编写一个排序算法。
That is an algorithm that takes a sequence of numbers as
这是一种将数字序列作为
input and puts them in ascending order from largest to smallest.
输入的算法，并将它们从大到小按升序排列。
For example, if you had the following input data,
例如，如果您有以下输入数据，则
you would want your algorithm to rearrange
需要您的算法重新排列
them so that you have this sequence: the same numbers,
它们，以便获得这样的序列：相同的数字，
but ordered from smallest to largest.
但从小到大排序。
Of course, what we did here,
当然，我们在这里所做的，
just reshuffled them all at once in a way that is very hard to generalize.
只是用一种很难一概而论的方式同时对它们进行了重新洗牌。
You will want to think of a more step-by-step way
您将需要考虑一种更逐步的方法
to sort your data for any sequence of numbers.
来对任何数字序列的数据进行排序。
Okay, so why think about sorting?
好吧，那为什么要考虑排序呢？
Well, for one thing,
好吧，首先，
sorting is an important and ubiquitous algorithm in Computer Science.
排序是计算机科学中一种重要且无处不在的算法。
For example, my email client lets me sort my messages by subject,
例如，我的电子邮件客户端允许我按主题
date, or a variety of other criteria.
、日期或其他各种标准对邮件进行排序。
Sorting data makes it easier to find what you need.
对数据进行排序可以更轻松地找到所需的内容。
When I am on Facebook,
当我在 Facebook 上
there is a list of trending stories.
时，有一份热门故事清单。
How would you get the most popular stories from a list of all stories?
如何从所有故事列表中获得最受欢迎的故事？
You would sort by popularity,
你可以按受欢迎程度进行排序，
then take the top items from the list.
然后从列表中选出排名靠前的项目。
Likewise, if I search google for something,
同样，如果我在谷歌上搜索一些东西，
it has many search results that might match my query,
它会有许多可能与我的查询相匹配的搜索
putting the results that are most likely to
结果，但会根据其排名对它们
be the best at the top of the results it displays.
进行排序，将最有可能最好的结果放在它显示的结果的顶部。
And of course, there are many other examples.
当然，还有很多其他的例子。
Another reason why we picked sorting for you to work on,
我们选择排序供你处理的另一个原因
is that there are many different correct ways to do it.
是，有许多不同的正确方法可以做到这一点。
It is good to learn that many problems have a lot of different solutions.
得知许多问题都有很多不同的解决方案，这真是太好了。
As you peer review other peoples solutions,
当你同行评审其他人的解决方案
you will hopefully see approaches that are different from what you thought of.
时，你有望看到与你想象的不同的方法。
And lastly, it is easy to verify that the answer is correct.
最后，很容易验证答案是否正确。
When you peer review someone else's algorithm,
当你同行评审别人的算法时，
you can easily check if they got the right answer for
你可以通过查看他们是否
some input data by looking to see if they put the data in the right order.
按正确的顺序排列数据，从而轻松检查他们对某些输入数据的答案是否正确。
So now let us put the seven steps to use and write a sorting algorithm.
因此，现在让我们使用七个步骤并编写一个排序算法。